But you only need to remember one thing.
Having our Tang Group develop Old Street
is nothing but beneficial for you.
And what if I disagree?
I hear (Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
Brother Shengzi
has some connection with Young Master Li of Jialong.
You know Li Xiangping?
I wouldn't say we're close.
But over the years,
I've had quite a few dealings
with Old Master Li.
Young Master Li just returned.
I was just thinking of finding a chance to meet him.
Second Master Tang,
you're even connected to forces in Jialong?
Could it be that behind you
is some immensely powerful figure?
Brother Shengzi knows too much.
That probably isn't good for you.
Just idle curiosity, idle curiosity.
Please don't take offense, Second Master.
The reason I called you here today
is to let you know
Old Street
is something I am determined to get.
If you
merely want wealth and status,
or to be esteemed in public,
I can satisfy you.
But if you insist on obstructing me,
even if you have the Li family's backing,
I can personally send you out of Bian Shui.
Brother Shengzi,
think it over carefully.
They all say you, Zhao Fengsheng,
are decisive and calm.
You must think this through very carefully.
This chocolate wrapper...
Dad...
Your dad just came up to break up your fight.
No idea who ambushed him.
I shouldn't have gotten into a fight.
You can scold me all you want.
Dad...
Don't stay silent, Dad.
Let's take Uncle back first.
Give me a hand.
Come on, come on.
My dad doesn't eat chocolate.
Could it have been left by the killer?
They say
if you follow Second Master,
you'll eat well
and drink well.
I'm certainly willing.
Good.
Brother Shengzi knows which way the wind blows.
I like young men like you.
What business do you want to manage?
Take your pick from here.
Second Master really knows how to enjoy life.
This stuff is delicious.
Tang Hongtu is likely connected to my dad's death.
I can't turn against him yet.
What?
Nothing catches your eye?
If it's all just these kinds of businesses,
Li Xiangping could give them to me.
I really can't muster any interest.
Then what do you want?
I want...
your life.
This casino.
Second Master!
This casino belongs to the young master!
Shut up.
Why the casino?
Because it makes money the fastest and the most.
You have vision.
You have ambition.
Truly worthy of being called Madman Zhao.
Very good.
From now on,
Brother Shengzi is the general manager of this casino.
Yes.
Ambitious enough.
That's the true spirit of youth.
I, Tang Hongtu, have room for your greed here.
Second Master,
truly a grand vision.
I'll go attend to business now.
Second Master,
Zhao Fengsheng only has a few thugs from Old Street.
Why are you so concerned about saving his face?
And you even gave him the casino?
Saving his face?
When have I, Tang Hongtu,
ever worried about a petty thug?
Then... what are you doing?
This Zhao Fengsheng is, after all, Li Xiangping's man.
Killing him outright would be hard to explain to the Li family.
Keeping him close
firstly,
prevents him from sabotaging the Old Street demolition.
Secondly,
it makes it easier to find a legitimate pretext
to eliminate Zhao Fengsheng.
Second Master is wise.
I'll go keep a close eye on him then.
Er Ni!
Where's Zhao Fengsheng?
Out fooling around somewhere again?
You've got Shengzi all wrong.
He's got something to handle recently.
He's busy.
What kind of thing can't even be told to me?
Darn it, Jin Jungang!
Covering for Zhao Fengsheng!
Are you still my brother or not?
I'm really not covering for him.
It's just that last time,
Chen Xiaobei introduced Shengzi to Tang Hongtu.
He's working at the Tang Group now.
You dare to believe Chen Xiaobei's words?
I'm going to find him.
Shengzi was afraid you'd act impulsively.
That's why he told me not to tell you.
Whatever you do, don't sell me out.
Where are you going?
I have important business to attend to.
Zhao Fengsheng
Not bad.
Shengzi.
Er Ni.
I'm at work.
What are you doing here?
You're my man, but you're not learning good things.
What if you get addicted to gambling and sell me off?
Quit your job right now.
What are you thinking about all day?
I suspect my dad's death...
...is related to the Tang Group.
I agreed to come work for Tang Hongtu...
...to investigate this secretly.
Uncle Zhao's death?
Right.
I wouldn't joke about something...
...like this with you.
Go home, hurry.
No.
If you're investigating something...
...you need someone to cover for you.
Besides...
You know my gambling skills.
As long as I'm here...
...they'll be too busy to watch you.
It's too dangerous for you. Get out of here.
I promise I'll just play cards.
I won't cause any trouble for you.
And also...
...not everyone here is from the Tang Group.
With so many people around, I won't get hurt.
Don't worry.
Er Ni.
Er Ni!
Xiaoman.
I've been looking for you for so long.
I thought you'd left Bian Shui.
Why are you back working for Ghost Face Hall?
I thought Old Street was my home.
I never thought in the end...
...this den of wolves would take me in.
The neighbors have come to their senses now.
Come back with me.
I don't want to go back.
Brother Gangzi.
Go ahead.
What do you need?
Old Street is going to be demolished, right?
I want to get a loan to buy up more land.
I didn't expect to run into you here.
Brother Gangzi...
...the news about Old Street's demolition...
...is known all over Bian Shui.
People coming to me for loans to buy land...
...are lining up for blocks.
If you're just playing around...
...you might not even get a spot.
Don't you know me?
When have I ever done things small?
Since I'm getting a loan...
...I'm going big.
How much do you want?
One million.
That's...
...not a small amount of money.
Xiaoman.
Don't worry.
Once the demolition compensation comes...
...I'll double my money.
When that happens...
...I'll take you to live a good life.
Brother Gangzi is still good to me.
I'll let you know once my application is ready.
It's good to have an insider handling things.
Alright.
Xiaoman...
...you really won't come back with me?
I'm fine here.
You should go back.
Wait for my good news.
Okay.
Brother Gangzi...
...I'm sorry.
I can't go back.
All of this...
...is Wuya's fault.
Hurry up.
Here are your cards.
Isn't this Master Mu?
Little girl.
Didn't you get enough of a beating last time?
You dare come to my turf again?
You run a casino.
You open your doors to welcome money.
I don't think Master Mu...
...would hit a pretty girl...
...right here, would he?
If you want to gamble, find a table.
But I didn't bring any money today.
I'd like to borrow some from Master Mu.
You dare come to gamble with no money?
How much do you want?
What's your interest rate here?
Thirty percent a month.
Fine.
Go get the money for me, sister.
Come with me.